{
    "subject": "Sandra_Goldbacher",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Me_Without_You__film_",
    "human_readable": "Sandra Goldbacher created the film Me Without You.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8574599623680115,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Sandra Goldbacher?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7442334294319153,
            "question": "Has Sandra Goldbacher won any awards for her work on Me Without You?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7004638314247131,
            "question": "Who directed the film Me Without You?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6177550554275513,
            "question": "Sandra Goldbacher is known for directing what kind of films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6087948679924011,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Sandra Goldbacher."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.608132004737854,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Sandra Goldbacher's films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5677105188369751,
            "question": "What year was the film Me Without You released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4892995357513428,
            "question": "Is Me Without You a documentary or a fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4471150040626526,
            "question": "What genre is the film Me Without You typically classified as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4144524037837982,
            "question": "What other projects has Sandra Goldbacher worked on besides directing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sandra Goldbacher created the film Me Without You.",
            "html": "yago_14855_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Me Without You typically classified as?",
            "html": "yago_14855_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Me Without You a documentary or a fictional film?",
            "html": "yago_14855_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Me Without You released?",
            "html": "yago_14855_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14855_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14855_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14855_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14855_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14855_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14855_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14855_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14855_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14855_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14855_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about Sandra Goldbacher's film \"Me Without You\", and it is explicitly stated that she wrote, directed, and produced the film. This suggests that Sandra Goldbacher created the film Me Without You."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Sandra Goldbacher directed and wrote the film \"Me Without You.\" For example, one of the documents states, \"2001 British film Directed bySandra GoldbacherWritten bySandra Goldbacher,\" directly supporting the statement that Sandra Goldbacher created the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}